Kunal Chandan

Computer Engineering Student

About

11 Four Winds Dr 14 M3J 1K7 Toronto, ON

kunalthechandan -@gmail.com kunalchandan.github.io Cell: (647)-785-1313

Languages

Bilingual English & Hindi Limited French

Programming

Java Python OpenCV-Octave/MATLAB PsychToolbox-HTML & JavaScript LaTeX

Interests

I take heavy interest in computer science, mainly in statistical analysis and machine learning. I first learned to program with Java in 2015, since then I have been improving my skills now I have some experience with Tensorflow, Octave, and OpenCV. I also lead Northview's FIRST robotics team and the programming team.

Education

2014–2018 High school Diploma

Northview Heights Secondary School

Specialist High Skills Major; Information Computer Tech. (SHSM - ICT)

Honours in Math, Science and Technology (HMST)

Experience

July '17-Curr. Elder Lab, York University

Research Internship.

Computer Vision, Machine Learning, and Psychophysics

-Learning to design neural networks for application in various projects i.e. Traffic tracking, hockey puck tracking

-Writing machine learning algorithms in Java, and Python using Keras and

-Writing scripts using Python and OpenCV for data augmentation and various

libraries for data visualization and interpretation
-MATLAB and PsychToolbox for designing psychophysics experiments

-Designing methods to gather crowd-sourced data with Amazon MTurk

July–Aug '17 Camp NAORCA, City of Toronto Camp Counsellor.

Voted Rookie of the year; outdoor youth summer camp

Jan '18 Northview Heights Secondary School Lead Programming Mentor

Mentored Northview's Co-Ed and All-girls programming teams

2017-2018 FIRST Team 6632, Supreme Robotics Build Executive

Lead and coordinated Supreme Robotics' build team

2016-2018 Private Tutoring Math& Science Tutor

Tutored children in math and science at local libraries.

Applications

2017-Curr. Personal Website kunalchandan.github.io

Various JavaScript applets, web-toys, and 3D Rendering done with Blender

2017-Curr. Various Psychophysics Experiments Research Internship related work

Designed and programmed psychophysics experiments similar to current re-

search in the Elder Lab

Other Extra-Curriculars

2014-Curr. Academic Clubs

-Programming Club Founder
-Biology Club Executive
-Physics Club Member
-Math Team Member
-DECA Chapter Executive
-SHSM-ICT President

-FIRST Robotics Build Executive

2014–Curr. Sports Clubs

-Cross Country Coach/Member

-Badminton Member -Water Polo Member

-Track & Field Coach/Member

Awards

2014-Curr. Academic Awards

-Co-op Award for Outstanding Achievement - Grade 12

-Business Award - Grade 9 & 10 -Honour Roll - All Semesters

-CCC Junior 1st place Northview - Grade 11

-ECOO Round 2 Finalist - Grade 11

-Toronto Finalist for Office Skills Competition - Grade 10 -Toronto Finalist for Robotics and Control Systems - Grade 11

2014–Curr. Athletic Awards

-Bronze Medallion for TDSSAA - Cross Country -Silver Medallion for TDSSAA - Track & Field